Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - F
        - Fo' Clips - Be thankful, 1995; SR-15725; Fo' Clips (Box 267)
          Catalog # QAL-630-DJ; A-side Matrix # QALS-630-A
          Dangerous Records
        - Fobert, Marcel - Rapfolie, 1984; SR-15726; Fobert, Marcel; Folie Club (Box 267)
          Catalog # Carrere-8347; A-side Matrix # 8347B
          Carrere
        - F.O.D. - No more, 1999; SR-15727; F.O.D. (Box 267)
          Catalog # PR10009-1; A-side Matrix # 25 PR-10009-1A
          Sumthing Else Music Works
        - F.O.D. - For my people, 1999; SR-15728; F.O.D. (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15729. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PR 1091-1; A-side Matrix # 25-PR-1091-1A
        - F.O.D. - For my people, 1999; SR-15729; F.O.D. (Box 267)
          In same jacket as # SR-15728. 2 copies.
        - FOE - Lifestyles; Consigliare Pt. 2, 1996; SR-15730; FOE (Box 267)
          Catalog # SPRO 30074; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30074-A
          Black Market Records
          Sacramento, California
        - FOE - Lifestyles; Consigliare Pt. 2, 1996; SR-15731; FOE (Box 267)
        - Foghat - Live, 1977; SR-15732; Foghat (Box 267)
          Catalog # BRK 6971; A-side Matrix # BRK-1-6971-JW-2
          Bearsville
        - F.O.H - Typhoon, 2000; SR-15733; F.O.H (Box 267)
          Catalog # VIBLP-F004; A-side Matrix # VIBLP-004-A2
          Vible Records
          Japan
        - Fonda Rae - EN2U, 2000; SR-15734; Fonda Rae (Box 267)
          Catalog # EN2U071; A-side Matrix # NOIZ01 B
          Noiz Records
        - Fonda Rae - EN2U, 2000; SR-15735; Fonda Rae (Box 267)
          Catalog # EN2U071; A-side Matrix # NOIZ01 A
        - Fonky Family - Hors-serie volume 1, 1999; SR-15736; Fonky Family (Box 268)
          Catalog # SMA 494093-1; A-side Matrix # 4940931000 1A1
          Côté Obscur
        - Fontaine, Peter - One moment in time, 1996; SR-15737; Fontaine, Peter (Box 268)
          Catalog # MRC 4514; A-side Matrix # MRC-4514-A
          Metropolitan Recording Corporation
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Fontaine, Peter - You are an angel, 1995; SR-15738; Fontaine, Peter (Box 268)
          Catalog # MRC 4507; A-side Matrix # MRC-4507-A
        - Fönz - Cruzin' in the Benz, 1992; SR-15739; Fönz (Box 268)
          Catalog # TR 301; A-side Matrix # TR 301-A
          Torain Records
        - Freddie Cruger - 3 foot high & rising (Disc one), 2006; SR-15740; Freddie Cruger; 3 Foot People (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # SR-15741. Double album.
          Catalog # HGLP001; A-side Matrix # HGLP-001-A
          Homegrown
          Sweden
        - Freddie Cruger - 3 foot high & rising (Disc two), 2006; SR-15741; Freddie Cruger; 3 Foot People (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # SR-15740. Double album.
          Catalog # HGLP001; A-side Matrix # HGLP-001-C
        - For Beauty's Sake - Backlash, 1988; SR-15742; For Beauty's Sake (Box 268)
          Catalog # MMD0008; A-side Matrix # MMD-0008-A
          Dream Records
        - For Beauty's Sake - Don't stop me now, 1987; SR-15743; For Beauty's Sake (Box 268)
          Catalog # MMD 0004; A-side Matrix # MMD-0004-A
        - For Real - Easy to love, 1994; SR-15744; For Real (Box 268)
          Catalog # 31458 8305 1; A-side Matrix # 31458 8305-1A SP-1 1-1
        - For Real - Like I do, 1996; SR-15745; For Real (Box 268)
          Catalog # RDP-5079; A-side Matrix # 75444-35079-1-SA-SP1
          Rowdy Records
        - Force - In the heat of the night, 1983; SR-15746; Force (Box 268)
          Catalog # BKD 515; A-side Matrix # BKD-515-A
          Becket Records
        - Force 5 - V-I-S-I-T-O-R-S '81, 1981; SR-15747; Force 5 (Box 268)
          Catalog # SPRO-7906; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7906-A-21
          Montage Records
        - Force Mass Motion - Feel it now; Infinity, 1998; SR-15748; Force Mass Motion (Box 268)
          Catalog # CUT 041; A-side Matrix # CUT 041-A1
          Rabbit City Records
        - Force M.D.'s - Here I go again, 1986; SR-15749; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          Catalog # TB 878; A-side Matrix # TB-878-A
        - Force M.D.'s - One plus one, 1986; SR-15750; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          Catalog # TB 886; A-side Matrix # TB-886A
        - Force M.D.'s - Are you really real?, 1990; SR-15751; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          Catalog # TB 956; A-side Matrix # TB-956-A
        - Force M.D.'s - Love letters, 1984; SR-15752; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          Catalog # TBLP 1003; A-side Matrix # TB-1003-A
        - Force M.D.'s - Touch and go, 1987; SR-15753; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          Catalog # TB 905; A-side Matrix # TB-905-A
        - Force M.D.'s - Let me love you, 1984; SR-15754; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # SR-15755. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TB 841; A-side Matrix # TB-841-A
        - Force M.D.'s - Let me love you, 1984; SR-15755; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # SR-15754. 2 copies.
        - Force M.D.'s - Tender love, 1985; SR-15756; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          Catalog # TB 876; A-side Matrix # TB-876-A
        - Force M.D.'s - Walking on air, 1986; SR-15757; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          Catalog # TB 890; A-side Matrix # TB-890-A
        - Force M.D.'s - Couldn't care less, 1987; SR-15758; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          Catalog # TB 909; A-side Matrix # TB-909-A
        - Force M.D.'s - Love is a house, 1987; SR-15759; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          Catalog # TB 898; A-side Matrix # TB-898-A
        - Force M.D.'s - Love is a house, 1987; SR-15760; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
        - Force M.D.'s - Forgive me girl, 1984; SR-15761; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # SR-15762. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TB 851; A-side Matrix # TB-851-A
        - Force M.D.'s - Forgive me girl, 1984; SR-15762; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # SR-15761. 2 copies.
        - Force M.D.'s - Walking on air, 1986; SR-15763; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
        - Force M.D.'s - Let me love you, 1984; SR-15764; Force M.D.'s (Box 268)
        - Ford, Paris - Drop da beat, 1995; SR-15765; Ford, Paris (Box 268)
          Catalog # P.E.G. 7431; A-side Matrix # PEG-7431-A
          Provocative Entertainment Group Inc
        - Ford, Paris - Ain't paid, 1995; SR-15766; Ford, Paris (Box 268)
          Annotated jacket
          Catalog # 1149V; A-side Matrix # 1149V A PIPO NYC
          Overlord Entertainment Group Inc
        - Ford, Paris - Drop da beat, 1995; SR-15767; Ford, Paris (Box 268)
        - Ford, Pennye - Dangerous, 1985; SR-15768; Ford, Pennye (Box 268)
          Catalog # TED1-2614; A-side Matrix # TED1-2614-AS-RCA1
          Total Experience Records
        - Ford, Willa - I wanna be bad (Disc one), 2001; SR-15769; Ford, Willa (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # ST-15770. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 300594; A-side Matrix # ST PR-90235-90236-1
          Lava
        - Ford, Willa - I wanna be bad (Disc two), 2001; SR-15770; Ford, Willa (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # ST-15769. Double album.
          Catalog # PR 300594; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-90239-1
        - Ford, Willa - F**k the men (A toast to men), 2003; SR-15771; Ford, Willa; May (Box 268)
          Catalog # PR 301326; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301326A-2
        - Forde, John - Stardance, 1977; SR-15772; Forde, John (Box 268)
          Catalog # 75008; A-side Matrix # 1-75008
        - Forecast - Happy days (Hip hip hooray), 1982; SR-15773; Forecast (Box 268)
          Catalog # JD-13298; A-side Matrix # PD-13298-A
        - Foreign Legion - Kidnapper van: beats to rock while bike stealin' (Instrumentals) (Disc one), 2000; SR-15774; Foreign Legion (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # ST-15775. Double album.
          Catalog # INSURB 9000-1; A-side Matrix # INSURB 9000-1 A
          Insidious Urban Records
          San Francisco, California
        - Foreign Legion - Kidnapper van: beats to rock while bike stealin' (Instrumentals) (Disc two), 2000; SR-15775; Foreign Legion (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # ST-15774. Double album.
          Catalog # INSURB 9000-1; A-side Matrix # INSURB 9000-1 C
        - Foreign Legion - Let me tell you something; Intangible MC's, 2001; SR-15776; Foreign Legion (Box 268)
          Catalog # IUR 9006-12; A-side Matrix # IUR-9006-12 A
        - Foremost Poets - Grave lifter, 1998; SR-15777; Foremost Poets (Box 268)
          Catalog # SOW-415; A-side Matrix # SOW415A
          Soundmen On Wax
        - Forman, Bonnie - All night, 1982; SR-15778; Forman, Bonnie (Box 268)
          Catalog # CM-120; A-side Matrix # CM-120-AM
          Wave
        - Format - Anything to make you love me; Whenever I call your name, 1994; SR-15779; Format (Box 268)
          Catalog # MRC 7002; A-side Matrix # MRC-7002 A
        - Formula V - Dance all night, 1977; SR-15780; Formula V (Box 268)
          Catalog # TCD-63; A-side Matrix # M-TCD-63-AS
          20th Century Records
        - Fort Knox Five - Dodge city rockers, 2003; SR-15781; Fort Knox Five (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # ST-15782. Different discs. Annotated.
          Catalog # FKX-001; A-side Matrix # FKX-001-A
          Fort Knox Recordings
          Washington, DC
        - Various - The foundations EP, 2003; SR-15782 (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # ST-15781. Different discs.
          Catalog # FKXP000; A-side Matrix # FKXP-0001-A
        - Fort Knox Five - Blowing up the barrio, 2004; SR-15783; Fort Knox Five (Box 268)
          Catalog # FKX-003; A-side Matrix # FKX-003-A
        - Fort Knox Five - Radio free D.C., 2005; SR-15784; Fort Knox Five (Box 268)
          Catalog # FKX005; A-side Matrix # 0504X24-A
        - Fort Knox Five - Brazilian hipster, 2004; SR-15785; Fort Knox Five (Box 268)
          Catalog # FKX004; A-side Matrix # FKX-004-A
        - Forté, John - Poly sci (Disc one), 1998; SR-15786; Forté, John (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # ST-15787. Double album.
          Catalog # C2S 41073; A-side Matrix # XSS-41274A-1B
          Ruffhouse Records
        - Forté, John - Poly sci (Disc two), 1998; SR-15787; Forté, John (Box 268)
          In same jacket as # ST-15786. Double album.
          Catalog # C2S 41073; A-side Matrix # XSS-41275A-1A
        - F.O.S. - Big black boots, 1993; SR-15788; F.O.S. (Box 268)
          Catalog # SBAB 75382-1; A-side Matrix # 72392 75382-1 SBAB 75382-1 RE 1
          Scotti Bros. Records
        - F.O.S. Project - Check it!, 2001; SR-15789; F.O.S. Project (Box 269)
          Catalog # FOS002; A-side Matrix # FOS002A
          FOS
        - Foster, Eboni - Everything you do (Disc one), 1998; SR-15790; Foster, Eboni (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15791. Double album.
          Catalog # MCA8P-4202; A-side Matrix # MCA 13276
        - Foster, Eboni - Everything you do (Disc two), 1998; SR-15791; Foster, Eboni (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15790. Double album.
          Catalog # MCA8P-4202; A-side Matrix # MCA 13278 SIDE 3
        - Foster, Tod - "Dancin" disco remix, 1979; SR-15792; Foster, Tod (Box 269)
          Catalog # MD 510; A-side Matrix # MD510A
        - Fuckin' Camels'n Effect - Slega la lega, 1992; SR-15793; Fuckin' Camels'n Effect; D.J. Fabri (Box 269)
          Catalog # CVX 004; A-side Matrix # CVX-004-A
          Century Vox Records
        - Foul Play Productions - Risk, 1998; SR-15794; Foul Play Productions (Box 269)
          Catalog # PART 017; A-side Matrix # PART-17-Y-1
          Partisan
        - Foundation - Boogie Down's got the flavor, 1996; SR-15795; Foundation; Rezidue (Box 269)
          Catalog # DB-5364; A-side Matrix # DB-5364-A
          Database Productions
        - Foundation 7 - Love ain't like this; Compredator, 1992; SR-15796; Foundation 7 (Box 269)
          Catalog # RK 001; A-side Matrix # RK 001 A
          Ruff Kutt Records
        - Four Tops - Indestructible, 1988; SR-15797; Four Tops (Box 269)
          Catalog # AD1-9705; A-side Matrix # AD-1-9075-SA-DMM1
        - Four Tops - Greatest hits, 1982; SR-15798; Four Tops (Box 269)
          Catalog # M5-209V1; A-side Matrix # M5-209V1-A-08A
        - Four Tops - Reach out I'll be there ('88 Remix), 1988; SR-15799; Four Tops (Box 269)
          Catalog # ZT 41944; A-side Matrix # ZT 41944 B2
        - Four Tops - Great songs and performances that inspired the Motown 25th anniversary television special, 1987; SR-15800; Four Tops (Box 269)
          Catalog # 2804ML; A-side Matrix # 5314ML-A-15A
        - Four Tops - Reach out I'll be there ('88 Remix), 1988; SR-15801; Four Tops (Box 269)
          Catalog # ZT 41944; A-side Matrix # ZT 41944 A2
        - Four Tops - Live and in concert, 1974; SR-15802; Four Tops (Box 269)
          Catalog # DSD-50188; A-side Matrix # DSD-50188-A
          ABC/Dunhill Records
        - Fourmula - Pass it over, 1993; SR-15803; Fourmula (Box 269)
          Catalog # EAS 5597; A-side Matrix # XSS5597A-1A
        - Fourplay - Sexual healing, 1996; SR-15804; Fourplay; El DeBarge (Box 269)
          Catalog # PRO-A-9312; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-9312-A-RE1-SR1
        - Fowler, Fred - Times are changin', 1988; SR-15805; Fowler, Fred (Box 269)
          Catalog # 4V9 43258; A-side Matrix # 4V9-43258-A-ES1
        - Fowler, Fred - Girl, you need a change of mind, 1986; SR-15806; Fowler, Fred (Box 269)
          Catalog # PS 2007; A-side Matrix # PS-2007-A
        - Fox, Frizzby - Pretty boys, 1987; SR-15807; Fox, Frizzby (Box 269)
          Catalog # 4Z9 06927; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-06927-3-1A
        - Fox, Samantha - I wanna have some fun, 1988; SR-15808; Fox, Samantha (Box 269)
          Catalog # 1155-1-JDAB; A-side Matrix # 1155-1-JD-A
        - Foxxx, Freddie - Searchin to find me, 1998; SR-15809; Foxxx, Freddie (Box 269)
          Catalog # KJ1FP98; A-side Matrix # KJ-1-FP-98-A
          KJAC Music
          Pound Ridge, NY
        - Foxx, Jamie - Experiment (The remixes), 1994; SR-15810; Foxx, Jamie (Box 269)
          Catalog # 07863-64238-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-64238-1A
          Fox Records
        - Foxx, Jamie - Peep this (Disc one), 1994; SR-15811; Foxx, Jamie (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15812. Double album.
          Catalog # 17863-66436-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-66436-1-A-DMM
        - Foxx, Jamie - Peep this (Disc two), 1994; SR-15812; Foxx, Jamie (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15811. Double album.
          Catalog # 17863-66436-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-66436-1-C-DMM
        - Foxxx, Freddie - Industry shakedown, 2000; SR-15813; Foxxx, Freddie; Bumpy Knuckles (Box 269)
          Catalog # KJAC 005; A-side Matrix # KJAC-005 A
        - Foxy - Party boys, 1980; SR-15814; Foxy (Box 269)
          Catalog # TKD-442; A-side Matrix # DASH 442 FOXY HAS MOXY
        - Foxy - Get off; Party boys, 1990; SR-15815; Foxy (Box 269)
          Catalog # HCL 2220; A-side Matrix # HCL-2220-A
          Hot Classics
        - Foxy - Get off; Tena's song, 1978; SR-15816; Foxy (Box 269)
          Catalog # TKD-88; A-side Matrix # TKD-88A
        - Frampton, Peter - Frampton comes alive (Disc one), 1976; SR-15817; Frampton, Peter (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15818. Double album.
          Catalog # SP-3703; A-side Matrix # SP-3709
          Scarborough, Ontario, Canada
        - Frampton, Peter - Frampton comes alive (Disc two), 1976; SR-15818; Frampton, Peter (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15817. Double album.
          Catalog # SP-3703; A-side Matrix # SP-3711
        - Frances, Helene - A woman alone; Woman - child, 1977; SR-15819; Frances, Helene (Box 269)
          Catalog # HIR-7772; A-side Matrix # 45-R-12678
          Hit International Records, Inc.
          Miami Beach, Florida
        - Franchi, Sergio - Laugh you silly clown; More (Theme from Mondo Cane), 1979; SR-15820; Franchi, Sergio (Box 269)
          Catalog # L33-1856; A-side Matrix # MCA-2057
          L.A. International Records
        - Franchise - Inside out, 1986; SR-15821; Franchise (Box 269)
          Catalog # PRS-1001; A-side Matrix # PRS-1001-A
          Panoramic Records South
        - Frankie Goes To Hollywood - Rage hard, 1986; SR-15822; Frankie Goes To Hollywood (Box 269)
          Catalog # DMD 987; A-side Matrix # STDM-50743-1
        - Frankie Goes To Hollywood - Relax, 1983; SR-15823; Frankie Goes To Hollywood (Box 269)
          Catalog # DMD 691; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-45793-2
        - Frankie Goes To Hollywood - Welcome to the Pleasuredome, 1985; SR-15824; Frankie Goes To Hollywood (Box 269)
          Catalog # DMD 830; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-47606-1
        - Frankie Hi-NRG MC - Faccio la mia cosa, 1993; SR-15825; Frankie Hi-NRG MC (Box 269)
          Catalog # X 004; A-side Matrix # X-004-A
          Irma
        - Frankie J. - Don't wanna try (Remixes), 2003; SR-15826; Frankie J. (Box 269)
          Catalog # CAS 59649; A-side Matrix # XSS 59649 A
          Sony Music Entertainment Inc.
        - Franklin, Aretha - Spirit in the dark, 1970; SR-15827; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          Catalog # SD 8265; A-side Matrix # ST-A-701975-EE
        - Franklin, Aretha - 30 Greatest hits (Disc one), 1986; SR-15828; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15829. Double album.
          Catalog # 81668-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-866021-E
        - Franklin, Aretha - 30 Greatest hits (Disc two), 1986; SR-15829; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15828. Double album.
          Catalog # 81668-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-866023-A
        - Franklin, Aretha - Rock-A-Lott, 1987; SR-15830; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          Catalog # AD1-9575; A-side Matrix # AD19575SAES2
        - Franklin, Aretha - Willing to forgive; Jump to it, 1994; SR-15831; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          Catalog # 07822-12702-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-2702-1-SB SP1-1
        - Franklin, Aretha - The first lady of soul (Disc one), 1985; SR-15832; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15833. Double album.
          Catalog # SMR 8506; A-side Matrix # DM B-3647 A-1/85 S 11
        - Franklin, Aretha - The first lady of soul (Disc two), 1985; SR-15833; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15832. Double album.
          Catalog # SMR 8506; A-side Matrix # DM B-3648 A-1/85 S 11
        - Franklin, Aretha - A rose is still a rose (The remixes) (Disc one), 1998; SR-15834; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15835. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-13484-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-13484-1-SA-RE1
        - Franklin, Aretha - A rose is still a rose (The remixes) (Disc two), 1998; SR-15835; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15834. Double album.
          Catalog # 07822-13484-1; A-side Matrix # 07822-13484-1-SC-RE1
        - Franklin, Aretha - Jumpin' Jack Flash, 1986; SR-15836; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          Catalog # AD1-9529; A-side Matrix # AD1-9529-SA
        - Franklin, Aretha - Aretha live at Fillmore West, 1971; SR-15837; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          Catalog # ATL 50 861; A-side Matrix # R/S Alsdorf 50861 A
        - Franklin, Aretha - Young, gifted and black, 1972; SR-15838; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          Catalog # SD 7213; A-side Matrix # ST-A-712393A
        - Franklin, Aretha - Think remix, 1998; SR-15839; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          Catalog # AA0298; A-side Matrix # AA-0298-A
        - Franklin, Aretha - What a fool believes, 1980; SR-15840; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          Catalog # SP-103; A-side Matrix # SP-103-SAL-CT 1
        - Franklin, Aretha - Rock steady, 1971; SR-15841; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15842. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 5046727630; A-side Matrix # 5046 727630-A1
        - Franklin, Aretha - Rock steady, 1971; SR-15842; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          In same jacket as # ST-15841. 2 copies.
        - Franklin, Aretha - Ain't nobody ever loved you, 1986; SR-15843; Franklin, Aretha (Box 269)
          Catalog # AD1-9473; A-side Matrix # AD1-9473-SA-ES 1
        - Franklin, Aretha - Jimmy Lee, 1986; SR-15844; Franklin, Aretha (Box 270)
          Catalog # AD1-9547; A-side Matrix # AD1-9547-AS-3
        - Franklin, Aretha - Jump to it; Just my daydream, 1982; SR-15845; Franklin, Aretha (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # ST-15846. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SP 138; A-side Matrix # SP-138-SA-ES 1
        - Franklin, Aretha - Jump to it; Just my daydream, 1982; SR-15846; Franklin, Aretha (Box 270)
          In same jacket as # ST-15845. 2 copies.
        - Franklin, Aretha - Get it right, 1983; SR-15847; Franklin, Aretha (Box 270)
          Catalog # AD 1 9043; A-side Matrix # AD1 9043-SA-ES 1
        - Franklin, Aretha - Here we go again, 1998; SR-15848; Franklin, Aretha (Box 270)
          Catalog # ADP-3493; A-side Matrix # ADP-3493-SA
        - Franklin, Aretha - Love me right, 1982; SR-15849; Franklin, Aretha (Box 270)
          Catalog # SP-147; A-side Matrix # SP-147
        - Franklin, Aretha - I knew you were waiting (For me), 1987; SR-15850; Franklin, Aretha; Michael, George (Box 270)
          Catalog # AD1-9560; A-side Matrix # AD1-9560-SA-ES 1
        - Franklin, Anthony - Hot number, 1983; SR-15851; Franklin, Anthony (Box 270)
          Catalog # DMD 611; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-44343-1
        - Franklin, Rodney - Bustin' out, 1987; SR-15852; Franklin, Rodney (Box 270)
          Catalog # CR12 023; A-side Matrix # CR12-023-A
          Criminal Records
        - Franklin, Rodney - Enuff is enuff, 1982; SR-15853; Franklin, Rodney (Box 270)
          Catalog # AS 1557; A-side Matrix # XSS 169124-1B
        - Franklyn, Chevelle - Nice & naughty, 1994; SR-15854; Franklyn, Chevelle (Box 270)
          Catalog # RDAB-62866-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-62866ASP1
        - Fraser, Andy - Do you love me, 1984; SR-15855; Fraser, Andy (Box 270)
          Catalog # DMD 709; A-side Matrix # ST DM 46016-2
        - Frantique - Strut your funky stuff, 1979; SR-15856; Frantique (Box 270)
          Catalog # 2Z8 3697; A-side Matrix # PIR-AG-2Z8-3697-3
          Philadelphia International Records
        - Frazier, Billy - Billy who?, 1980; SR-15857; Frazier, Billy; Billy Frazier and Friends (Box 270)
          Catalog # 001 A; A-side Matrix # BILJUMA-001-A
          Biljuma Records
        - Freakaristic - Life (Tough world-rough times), 1987; SR-15858; Freakaristic (Box 270)
          Catalog # 234.789; A-side Matrix # 234-789 A 1
          Injection Disco Dance Label
        - Freakaristic - Money, 1990; SR-15859; Freakaristic (Box 270)
          Catalog # 134.911.6; A-side Matrix # MS134911 A 4C1
        - Freakazoids - @tic futura, 1998; SR-15860; Freakazoids (Box 270)
          Catalog # ZOID 001; A-side Matrix # 08 40245 20 1B1 ZOID 001
          Zoid Recordings
        - Freaknasty - Down low, 1997; SR-15861; Freaknasty (Box 270)
          Catalog # TR 1122-1; A-side Matrix # TR1122-A
          Power Records
          Norcross, Georgia
        - Freakniks - Under the sun remixed (Part two), 1997; SR-15862; Freakniks (Box 270)
          Catalog # SC 008; A-side Matrix # SC008 A-1
          Scenario Records
        - Freakniks - Under the sun remixed (Part one), 1997; SR-15863; Freakniks (Box 270)
          Catalog # SC 007; A-side Matrix # SC007 A-1
        - Freakpower - No way, 1998; SR-15864; Freakpower (Box 270)
          Catalog # 74321 578571; A-side Matrix # NO WAY-1-A1 (74321-57857-1)
          Deconstruction
        - Freaky - Time and age, SR-15865; Freaky (Box 270)
          Catalog # HYP 4Y; A-side Matrix # HYP 4Y-A1
          Hyper Records
        - Freddy B - It’s the hip hop, 1985; SR-15866; Freddy B; Mighty Mike Masters (Box 270)
          Catalog # TUF 120012; A-side Matrix # TUF-120012-A
          Tuff City
          Long Island City, New York